(This story is entirely fictional)
You made a mess of this.
I don't need your help.
Put it down.
Okay.
(Based on the novel
Doctor Qin: Executer)
It's been a long time.
Come on in.
Ms. Song.
Mom, this is Qin Ming,
your student.
Qin Ming?
The one from Class 8?
You were so good at math,
always near the top of your grade,
but not so good at English, right?
Yes.
Look at the weather.
Will it rain tomorrow?
Have I watered them?
You called her... Mom?
Ms. Song is sick.
She's becoming more forgetful.
Have a seat.
You've lost weight.
You're much thinner
than you were in school.
Is work tough?
Not really.
What do you do?
Mom.
The food's getting cold.
Let's go eat.
Oh, right.
Let's eat.
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 5=
Thank you.
Mom was right.
You are thinner
than you were in high school.
Eat more.
You're the same.
Really?
And yet you're different.
I had the class monitor
give you my number.
If I didn't call you,
when were you planning to contact me?
(Jin Keke, I like you.)
Were you waiting for the main course?
Yeah!
Qin Ming.
Do you have any questions for me?
Yes.
Too many.
I don't know how to start.
Then let me go first.
You must be wondering
why I'm with Ms. Song.
Three years ago,
I ran into her at the hospital.
She'd been diagnosed with Alzheimer's.
She was all alone.
And so was I.
Two people together
may make things feel warmer.
Later,
her condition got worse.
She often mistook me
for Xia Wen.
At first, I'd explain.
But later,
I gave up.
I just answered
to whatever she called me.
As long as she was happy.
Actually,
I'm glad I can take care of her
in Xia Wen's place.
You dropped out of school
because of Xia Wen?
Qin Ming, all these ten years,
finding out my number
would've been easy.
But you never came looking for me.
And ten years later,
you're still only interested
in what happened back then?
Ten years ago, you just left.
I asked you the same question back then.
You never answered me.
Qin Ming, you should go.
I'm not your suspect.
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
No one knows how much I regret
not going home with her that day.
I should've gone home with her.
Wherever she went,
I should've gone with her.
I should've gone home with her.
Bad boy!
Did you bully Wen?
Go now!
Don't be afraid.
Mom's here.
No one will bully you.
Qin Ming.
All these years,
I've had the same dream over and over.
What dream?
Maybe next time.
I'll tell you when we meet again.
See you next time.
(Fan A 65523)
(Run...)
The fingerprint on the window board
indeed matches Le Tianyi.
We've figured out his background.
He's not a local.
He came here ten years ago
to make a living.
He started out as a deliveryman.
No education, no connections.
How did a delivery guy like him
make VP at Sun Group?
It was all thanks to Wang Xuan.
She's a Longfan native,
got divorced and had a child.
So he married her.
Then, through her family's connections,
he worked his way up.
A classic social climber.
Someone like him
must be deeply insecure
and desperate to prove himself.
With a strong female boss like Su Shi,
he must've really resented her.
To her face,
he was both jealous and afraid,
and showed her great respect.
But behind her back,
who knows how many times
he betrayed her.
Are the shoeprints at the scene
also Le Tianyi's?
The size matches.
They're all size 44.
According to our interviews,
he often goes hiking in Fengshan.
He knows the area well.
Could he be the Executer?
That fingerprint's too clean.
Someone who claims to be the Executer
would slip up like that?
Mr. Dong, you mean...?
Find out
whether that fingerprint was a slip-up
or an attempt to mislead us.
Either way,
we'll summon Le Tianyi
first thing tomorrow.
Who the heck are you?
Who are you?
Let me go.
I'm talking to you!
Let me go!
Le Tianyi,
I suggest you stay still.
Otherwise,
I guarantee you'll see Su Shi very soon.
Let me go!
I'm talking to you!
Let me go. Now!
I said...
Look here.
What's wrong?
You look so pale.
Where did I go last night?
You don't remember?
We were home celebrating Niu's birthday.
Look.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to me!
Where's Niu?
I took her to her grandma's.
Yesterday...
I was home? Didn't go out?
Didn't go anywhere?
You didn't.
Who do you want?
You.
Come with us.
Last night,
I was home with my wife,
celebrating our girl's birthday.
There are videos and photos on my phone.
Look for yourself.
Then explain to me
why your fingerprints
and shoeprints
were found at Su Shi's crime scene.
Le Tianyi, I'm talking to you!
Feeding the cats.
I was there to feed the cats.
That isn't a crime, right?
As far as I know,
you and Su Shi didn't get along.
Yet you fed her cats?
There are bound to be conflicts at work.
We were just putting on a show.
Sometimes one plays the good cop
and the other the bad cop.
Oh, right.
I'm allergic
to cat hair.
So I made sure to wear gloves.
Then why would there
be my fingerprints?
Also,
you mentioned
the shoeprints, right?
They were from this pair, size 44.
They were my prints.
Le Tianyi,
watch your attitude.
Show some respect.
Oh,
my bad.
I was worked up.
They were from my shoes.
I admit it, of course.
That's my shoe size,
(Sound Laws, Strict Enforcement)
size 44.
(Fair Justice, Universal Compliance)
But I don't think it's fair to say
that just because my shoeprints
and my fingerprints were there,
I'm involved in this case.
I mean,
you can't just say that, right?
All right.
We'll stop here for today.
Can I go now?
Sure.
(Contact Card)
Officer Han Liang.
If you think of anything else,
give me a call anytime.
Sure.
I'm leaving.
Watch your attitude.
Okay. Sorry.
Why is there a flower?
You brought it home.
Why would I bring this home?
Are you too tired?
You did bring it home.
Why would I bring this home?
Look at it!
Why would I bring it home?
This lousy thing!
Come here!
Look at it.
No words.
Listen to me.
Tell me.
Where did it come from?
You really brought it home.
No way!
Nonsense!
Tell me. Where did it come from?
You really brought it home!
You really did.
You did.
Tell me. Where did it come from?
Tell me! Where did it come from?
You really brought it home.
Who is it?
Delivery.
Coming.
The flowers you ordered.
Happy birthday.
Get lost!
Sir?
Your sunflowers!
Thanks for coming so late.
I just made some soup.
Have some before it gets cold.
Thank you, Ms. Song.
Well,
my condition comes and goes.
I don't even remember
what I was like
the last time you saw me.
Don't mind me.
Of course not.
I know all about your condition.
By the way, is Keke home?
You're not here to see me.
You're here to see Keke, aren't you?
She's working at the supermarket.
She'll be back soon.
Okay.
Here, have some soup.
Drink up.
It's good.
Oh, Ms. Song.
Last time I was here,
I saw your note
about buying tissues, oil,
and trash bags this Wed.
I just got them for you.
Really?
See? I don't even remember.
Thank you, Erbao.
Well,
later,
I'll have Wen transfer the money to you.
No need, Ms. Song.
Right.
Ms. Song, are you cooking something?
Wait, a bottle of liquor?
Oh, it's cooking oil.
I'll need it tomorrow.
(Need help? Call your daughter Keke.)
(Need anything? Call your son Qin Ming.)
(On the tower,
hypocrites build their nests.)
It's all fake.
It's all an illusion.
I'm just under too much stress.
Next,
it's your turn.
♪Moonlight soaks the withered sunflower♪
♪Fingerprints seal the verdict♪
♪Good deeds bloom from lies♪
♪Who's next nailed to this wall?♪
♪The Executer is never late♪
♪Every sin will be paid for♪
♪When gears crush the hypocrite's crown♪
♪The crocodile will kiss the collector♪
♪Hear the hymn of bones torn down♪
♪In the shredder,
peace and equality are found♪
♪The sunflower bows, reciting names♪
♪Each petal is a solemn phrase♪
♪And moonlight, forever fair♪
♪Lights up crime and punishment♪